homewise.co.in 2013-06-06

# Netambit Homewise

As a registered member of NHO, you authorize us & our associate partners to contact you via email or phone call and offer you their services for the product you have opted for, imparting product knowledge, offer promotional offers running on website & offers offered by the associated third-parties. Irrespective of the fact if also you have registered yourself under DND or DNC service, you still authorize us to give you a call from the NHO & associate partners for the above mentioned purposes till 45 days of your registration with us.

In addition, look forward to receiving monthly newsletters and exclusive promotions offering special deals.

This Privacy Policy covers NHO's treatment of personally identifiable information that NHO collects when you are on the NHO site, and when you use NHO's services. This policy also covers NHO's treatment of any personally identifiable information that NHO's business partners share with NHO. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that NHO does not own or control or to people that NHO does not employ or manage.

NHO collects personally identifiable information when you register for a NHO account, when you use certain NHO products or services, when you visit pages of homewise.co.in. NHO may also receive personally identifiable information from our business partners.

When you register with NHO, we ask for your first name, last name, state, city, email, birth date, and gender. Once you register with NHO and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. 

Also during registration, you may be requested to register your mobile phone and email id, pager, or other device to receive text messages, notifications, and other services to your wireless device. By registration you authorize us to send SMS /email alerts to you for your login details and any other service requirements or some advertising messages /emails from us.

Please note that we review our Privacy Policy from time to time, and we may make periodic changes to the policy in connection with that review. Therefore, you may wish to bookmark this page and/or periodically review this page to make sure you have the latest version. Regardless of later updates, we will abide by the privacy practices described to you in this Privacy Policy at the time you provided us with your personal information.

## Information Sharing and Disclosure 

NHO will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone other than as specifically noted herein. Notwithstanding the foregoing, NHO may sell and/or transfer your personally identifiable information to an affiliate and to any successor-in-interest as a result of a sale of any part of NHO’s business or upon the merger, reorganization or consolidation of NHO with another entity on a basis that NHO is not the surviving entity. For the purposes of this paragraph, "affiliate" means any person directly, or indirectly through one or more intermediaries, that controls, is controlled by or is under common control with NHO. The term “control”, as used in the immediately preceding sentence, shall mean with respect to any person, the possession, directly or indirectly, of the power, through the exercise of voting rights, contractual rights or otherwise, to direct or cause the direction of the management or policies of the controlled person. As used in this Privacy Policy, the term "person" includes any natural person, corporation, partnership, limited liability company, trust, unincorporated association or any other entity.

## Third-Party Advertising 

We may use third-party advertising companies and/or ad agencies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

## Online Surveys

NHO values opinions and comments from members, so we frequently conduct online surveys. Participation in these surveys is entirely optional. Typically, the information is aggregated, and used to make improvements to the homewise.co.in site and its services and to develop appealing content, features and promotions for homewise.co.in site members. Survey participants are anonymous unless otherwise stated in the survey.

## Legal

We strictly follow the norms of non-disclosure agreement. It is our endeavor to ensure that the websites linked to us are safe and secure. However we have no control over 3rd party websites. Given our legal responsibilities to legal authorities and regulators, there may be situations when we need to share your information with legal authorities or processes or need to protect our right or comply by terms and conditions.

## Other sites

There might be affiliates or other sites linked to our web site. Personal information that you provide to those sites are not our property. The affiliated sites may have different privacy practices and we encourage you to read their privacy policies. These sites may place their cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information.

## Privacy Policy Changes

NHO may amend this policy from time to time, at our discretion. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting the changes here on these Privacy Policy pages.

## Automatic Logging of Session Data

We automatically log generic information about your computer's connection to the Internet, which we call "session data", that is anonymous and not linked to any personal information. Session data consists of things such as IP address, operating system and type of browser software being used and the activities conducted by the user while on homewise.co.in site. An IP address is a number that lets computers attached to the internet, such as our web servers, know where to send data back to the user, such as the pages of the site the user wishes to view. We collect session data because it helps us analyze such things as what items visitors are likely to click on most, the way visitors are clicking through the site, how many visitors are surfing to various pages on the site, how long visitors to the site are staying and how often they are visiting. It also helps us diagnose problems with our servers and lets us better administer our systems. Although such information does not identify any visitor personally, it is possible to determine from an IP address a visitor's Internet Service Provider (ISP), and the approximate geographic location of his or her point of connectivity.  

## Cookies

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. There are many myths circulating about cookies, but you should know that cookies are only read by the server that placed them, and are unable to do such things as run programs on your computer, plant viruses or harvest your personal information. The use of cookies is very common on the Internet and NHO's use of cookies is similar to that of such sites as Expedia and Orbitz, as well as Yahoo!, CNN.com and other reputable online companies.

First and foremost, you can rest assured that no personally identifiable information ("PII") about you (e.g., name, address, etc.) is gathered or stored in the cookies placed by the homewise.co.in site and, as a result, none can be passed on to any third-parties.

Cookies allow us to serve you better and more efficiently, and to personalize your experience at our site. NHO uses cookies to personalize your experience on the homewise.co.in site, and with respect to advertisements. As to the former, these types of cookies allow you to log in without having to type your log-in name each time (only your password is needed. We may also use such cookies to display an advertisement to you while you are on homewise.co.in site or to send you a "Best Day to Buy" email (or similar emails - assuming you have not opted out of receiving such emails) focusing on destinations in which we think you might be interested. None of this information is passed to any third party, and is used solely by us to provide you with a better user experience on homewise.co.in site.

A cookie may also be placed by our advertising server. Such cookies are used only for purposes of tracking the effectiveness of advertising served by us on our site and no Personally Identifiable Information (PII) is gathered from you by the use of these cookies, nor is this information shared with any third parties. Similarly, a cookie may be placed by our third-party advertising companies. These companies may use aggregated statistics about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about travel-related goods and services that you may be interested in. The information they collect does not include your PII.

The third-party advertising companies may also employ technology that is used to measure the effectiveness of ads. Any such information is anonymous. They may use this anonymous information about your visits to this and other sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of potential interest to you. No PII is collected during this process. The information is anonymous, and does not link online actions to an identifiable person. 

Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies. Of course, by changing the options on your web browser or using certain software programs, you can control how and whether cookies will be accepted by your browser. NHO supports your right to block any unwanted Internet activity, especially that of unscrupulous websites. However, blocking NHO cookies may disable certain features on the homewise.co.in site, and may make it impossible to purchase or use certain services available on the homewise.co.in site. Please note that it is possible to block cookie activity from certain websites while permitting cookies from sites you trust, like NHO.

## Disclaimer

Visitors to this website/portal and every third party are hereby informed that the owners of this website/portal are not the agents or intermediaries of the insurers, whose products are dealt with in this website/portal. They are also not the sub-agents or sub-intermediaries of the agents and intermediaries of the respective insurers. Though endeavour is made to make correct policy/product comparisons, quotes, features, etc., based on the information provided by the insurers or its agents or intermediaries, it is made abundantly clear that the directors, shareholders, officers and employees and homewise.co.in are in no way responsible to or liable for any one for his / her investment decision, and every prospect/ investor/policyholder shall be solely responsible for the consequences of his/her decision.

Thank you for using homewise.co.in !!!! ****
